

About me

I am a web developer with the ability to quickly adapt to any development environment, I am capable of performing very good teamwork, either leading or following, in order to provide solutions to problems.

Expertise Skill

• Html

- MongoDB
- Css(sass, bem, itcss) Mysql
- Javascript
- Git

- React
- NodeJs
- Github

Contact Me

- **(a)** +57 3108672765
- 🙀 christianjavieruizcortes@gmail.com
- https://mugen-portfolio.vercel.app/

CHRISTIAN JAVIER RUIZ CORTÉS

WEB DEVELOPMENT

Education

2021-2022

• Full Stack Web Development bootcamp Educamás Bogotá, Colombia Cra 13 # 83 -19

Work Experience

Full Stack Web Developer Freelancing 2020-Currently

• design and development of different web applications using modern technologies.

Full Stack Web Developer Educamás 2021-2022

• Development of different web applications using modern technologies, both from the client side and from the server side.

Languages

- Native spanish
- Advanced english certificated: https://acortar.link/cmHBsF